How lucky I am to meet you in this desolate place.
My name is Ines Hom.
Please help [cough].
You are my only hope.
I got the
flu [cough] from a toad while working in the swamp.
Only a special healing potion can
save me.
The potion was supposed to arrive with a
caravan yesterday,
but bandits ambushed the caravan
and stole the potion.
If I don't take the potion by
tomorrow [cough],
I'll die.
Please bring me the potion [cough],
I don't want to die yet!
I was able to find out that the
bandit camp is behind the next
door.
I'd like to, but unfortunately I
'm too weak to storm the camp myself
.
You, on the other hand, look very strong.
Bandits always hide their loot
inside the camp.
You'll probably
have to go there to get the potion.
You're right, it's not that simple.
The bandits have divided their camp into individual
rooms, and
you need a key for each room.
The bandits carry the keys with
them.
For each key, you must defeat a bandit and take the key
.
Don't even try to steal the keys from the bandits - you only stand a chance in an open
battle.
Why should I lie to you?
If you have a key,
you can use it to open the next
door.
A key only ever fits on
one door.
The camp starts behind the door at the
end of the corridor. Here you have the
key.
There are sneaky traps all over the camp
, so watch out. Did
you understand everything so far?
Good, please bring me the potion so I
don't have to die!
I thank you.
is there anyone
This is our camp, get out!
Who's there?
Now it's going round!
I'll have you soon. Say goodbye to your life!
Is someone coming?
Intruder, you will pay for this!
We are bandits. Sneaking is useless!
We are bandits.
Resistance is futile!
Come here if you dare.
This is your end!
Pull the lever to open the gate!
Excuse me, but I secretly
followed you.
I see you defeated the bandits and recovered the potion.
I knew you could do this.
Many Thanks. you saved my life
I am deeply indebted to you.